You can't contain evil.
It Lives Inside is a horror, mystery film directed by Bishal Dutta.
Desperate to fit in at school, Sam rejects her Indian
culture and family to be like everyone else.
However, when a mythological demonic spirit latches onto her former best
friend, she must come to terms with her heritage to defeat it.
Samidha, played by Megan Suri.
Poorna, played by Neeru Bajwa.
Tamira, played by Mohana Krishnan.
Joyce, played by Betty Gabriel.
Inesh, played by Vik Sahay.
Russ, played by Gage Marsh.
It Lives Inside is a 2023 supernatural horror film written and directed by Bishal Dutta and starring Megan Suri, and
follows Sam, an Indian-American teen trying to fit into her suburban high school by rejecting her heritage.
When Sam unleashes a terrifying, ancient Indian demon that feeds on loneliness and trauma, it kidnapps her best friend Tamira
and then targeting Sam, forcing her to confront her identity and cultural roots to save her friend and herself.
The film also stars Neeru Bajwa, Mohana Krishnan, Vik Sahay,
Gage Marsh, Beatrice Kitsos, and Betty Gabriel.
It Lives Inside had debuted at the 2023 South by Southwest film
festival, and was released by Neon on September 22, 2023.
The film received mixed reviews from critics and
had grossed $7.5 million worldwide.
The film explores themes of supernatural, based on myths, legends or
folklore, supernatural horror, indian american, horror.
The tone is dark and mind_bending.